<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Barcode Store India</string>
    <string name="title_activity_search_products">SearchProducts</string>
    <string name="transition">transit</string>

    <string name="about_page_description" translatable="false">ATM Group Of Companies</string>
    <string name="about_page_description1" translatable="false">The Company has been promoted by some highly experienced Professionals dedicated to provide total IT solutions under one roof. It possesses not only the latest technology gadgets but also the most knowledgeable and experience hands to offer most user friendly customized solutions. \n\nThe business philosophy of the company is to lay emphasis on Human Values and Personal Relations.At ATM Technology meets emotions and limits are higher than the sky. Great stress is laid on proper communication, transparency and human relationship, which forms an integral part of the corporate culture. At ATM, we not only develop products but we develop relationships.\n\nWe at ATM believe in teamwork. With every new day the quest for acquiring new competencies continues. Forever searching, experimenting, innovating, learning, moving ahead with our sincere efforts and dedication, shaping the future, and challenging our competencies to create new opportunities, is a never-ending process in the company.</string>

    <string name="about_contact_us">Contact us</string>
    <string name="about_twitter1">+91 961 990 07 85 (RMA)</string>
    <string name="about_twitter2">+91 966 400 80 90 (RMA)</string>
    <string name="addRma">022 6592 4421 (RMA)</string>
    <string name="addAndroid">022 6532 4421 (Android Support)</string>
    <string name="addwins1">022 6512 4421 (Windows Support)</string>
    <string name="addwins2">022 6542 4421 (Windows Support)</string>
    <string name="addwins3">022 6552 4421 (Windows Support)</string>
    <string name="addweb">022 6562 4421 (Web Support)</string>
    <string name="about_twitter3">+91 961 990 07 85 (Support)</string>
    <string name="about_twitter4">+91 993 069 99 01 (Support)</string>
    <string name="about_website">Visit our website ( ATM Infotech )</string>

    <string name="PH">Printer Problems</string>

    <string name="GT_800">Zebras GT Series and GT800 desktop printers combine dependable printing with fast print speeds and network manageability. With their easy-to-use design, Zebraís advanced desktop printers enable you to improve operational efficiencies.</string>
    <string name="GC_420t">The GC420t thermal transfer printer and the GC420d direct thermal printer are Zebraís most affordable desktop printers. A cost effective way to print labels to keep your business moving.</string>

    <string name="ZT_230">Zebra incorporated extensive customer feedback, as well as the legacy of our industry leading Stripe and S4M printers, to create the new ZT200 Series family of printers with elegant space-saving design, effortless setup, intuitive user operation, and ease of service and maintenance.</string>
    <string name="ZT_410">Keep your critical operations running efficiently. Constructed with an all-metal frame and bi-fold door, ZT400 Series printers deliver advancements in print speed, registration and connectivity as well as additional advanced features.</string>
    <string name="ZT_110xi">Streamline operations with an innovative high-volume RFID encoder and printer. Print and encode a variety of UHF radio frequency identification smart labels for a number of applications, including healthcare specimen smart labelling, item-level tagging and more.</string>
    <string name="GX_430">Offering top print quality and a variety of connectivity options, the GX430 printer support the widest range of applications and can be integrated into almost any environment so that you can improve efficiency and profitability, save time and reduce operator training.</string>
    <string name="ZD_500R">Offering high-resolution print quality and quadruple connectivity options, the ZD500 is compact and feature-packed for top performance. A Link-OS-enabled printer, it is easy to integrate, manage and maintain from any location. Runs in direct thermal or thermal transfer mode.</string>

    <string name="Zebra_Scanner_LS_1203">Designed to meet the needs of small businesses, the LS1203 provides the performance and features needed to significantly reduce data entry errors and boost productivity day in and day out in gift shops, boutiques, sporting goods, jewelers, video stores, florists and other small local retailers.</string>
    <string name="Zebra_Scanner_LS_2208_With_Stand">The LS2208 is designed for continuous usage all day, which significantly reduces downtime and repair costs. It provides accurate, first-time scanning. And since it is always ready for the next scan, the LS2208 can shorten check-out lines, improve customer service and increase productivity.</string>
    <string name="Zebra_Scanner_LS_2208_Without_Stand">The affordable Symbol LS2208 handheld barcode scanner provides fast, reliable scanning in an ergonomic, lightweight form. The wide working range ófrom near-contact to 17 inches ó makes this device ideal for retail, hospital, education or government settings. Multiple on-board interfaces ensure integration with a variety of host systems.</string>
    <string name="Zebra_Scanner_LI_4278">The LI4278 takes 1D barcode scanning to the next level, allowing workers to scan faster and farther as they can capture virtually any 1D barcode. </string>
    <string name="Zebra_Scanner_DS_4208">This Barcode Scanner is discontinued. Replacement Model: DS4308</string>
    <string name="Zebra_Scanner_DS_4308">The DS4308 does it all ó 1D or 2D, electronic or printed on paper labels or plastic cards, even if the barcode is dirty, scratched or poorly printed. With PRZM Intelligent Imaging inside, your workers can capture barcodes as fast as they can pull the scan trigger. And that means no more Point-of-Sale exceptions that can turn into longer lines, longer wait times and lost sales. The DS4308 ó a new class of scanner for a new world of barcodes.</string>
    <string name="Zebra_Scanner_DS_3600">The practically indestructible 1D LI3608 corded and LI3678 cordless scanners are ready for the world’s toughest environments — the warehouse and manufacturing floor.</string>
    <string name="Zebra_Scanner_DS_6878">The DS6878 cordless 2D imager offers the complete data capture functionality required to streamline and error-proof everyday processes. Comfortable and easy-to-use, this single device can capture all common barcodes (1D, 2D and PDF417) on labels as well as on mobile phone displays.</string>
    <string name="Zebra_Scanner_DS_7708">When it comes to on-counter scanning, the DS7708 offers a feature set that puts it at the top of its class for performance, ease of deployment and total cost of ownership. No matter what barcodes appear at your POS, the DS7708 can scan them all; 1D, 2D, printed and electronic.</string>
    <string name="Zebra_Scanner_DS_9208">Whether you need a barcode scanner that can be used on paper labels or mobile barcodes on the screen of a mobile phone, with the Zebra DS9208, youíll be ready. You get the versatility to scan any 1D or 2D barcode ó from the printed labels in retail that identify product and pricing at the register to mobile coupons, mobile gift and loyalty cards, boarding passes and even theater tickets.</string>

    <string name="MC_3200">Redefine productivity and reliability with the MC3200 mobile computer, the next generation in the class-leading MC3000 Series, now with more options to meet your needs. Choose the right operating system for your business ñ Androidô Jelly Bean or Microsoftô Embedded Compact 7. Your choice of our most advanced 1D laser or 1D/2D imager scan engine allows your workers to easily capture barcodes in any condition.n</string>
    <string name="MC_36_1D">With the MC36, you can have it all. Your workers get the modern design they want along with an operating system that is comfortable and familiar </string>
    <string name="MC_36_2D">With the MC36, you can have it all. Your workers get the modern design they want along with an operating system that is comfortable and familiar </string>
    <string name="MC_9200">The MC9200 is the next generation in the MC9000 Series, the industry’s gold standards for mobility in inventory and asset management in the most demanding environments — from the warehouse floor to the dock door.</string>
    <string name="MC_2180_1D">With the value-priced MC2180, get the features you need ñ from rugged design and superior ergonomics to powerful processing to the get the job done.</string>
    <string name="MC_2180_2D">With the value–priced MC2180–1D, get the features you need from rugged design and superior ergonomics to powerful processing to the get the job done.</string>
    <string name="MC_45">The MC45 is the affordable way to give your workers the real-time information they need to get the job done right, right on the spot, preventing lost sales ó and lost customers. Your workers get the sleek consumer styling and one-handed operation they expect, along with the features, durability, security and manageability your business demands.</string>
    <string name="MC_67">Give your field workforce the tools they need to work faster and smarter with the rugged MC67 Series. This fully-featured device lets workers access information in your backend system; scan practically any barcode in almost any condition; capture documents to simplify recordkeeping; take and send video and photos for real-time repair support; and call a customer with an arrival window. </string>
    <string name="MC_919_Z">To put more product into the hands of your customers and put more profit into your pockets you need to know what you have and where to find it. On the dock or in the storeroom, the MC919Z Handheld RFID Reader is designed to make that job faster and easier.</string>
    <string name="MC_319_Z">The MC319-Z is half the weight of its industrial counterparts and is the lightest UHF RFID rugged handheld reader on the market period. Its well-balanced, gun-style grip brings comfort to the most read-intensive applications. And the advanced, high efficiency Zebra RFID reader engine increases workforce productivity with faster read rates that increase throughput.</string>

    <string name="EZ_320">This rugged printer is sure to become a productive and efficient addition to your workplace thanks to its innovative design. </string>
    <string name="QLN_220">Optimized for the high duty-cycle applications where 2" (48mm) labels and tags are needed, and can also print receipts.</string>

    <string name="Zebra_ZXP_3">Reliable and easy to use, the ZXP Series 3 is everything you could want in a professional card printer. The ZXP Series 3 is an ideal solution for low- to medium-volume single or dual-sided printing applications that require minimal operator training and excellent print quality. ZXP Series 3 printers offer advanced features and high capacity media options.</string>
    <string name="Zebra_ZXP_7">The ZXP Series 7 is Zebra highest performance printer for any direct-to-card printing application.</string>
    <string name="Zebra_ZXP_8">Increase operational efficiency and lower costs without sacrificing image quality. This card printer lets you create on-demand picture-perfect plastic cards. </string>

    <string name="Zebra_Card_Studio">Extend your card design capabilities with Zebra CardStudio card printer software. This simple-to-learn, yet feature-rich software makes loyalty card, gift card, and ID card design easy.</string>
    <string name="Zebra_Designer_Pro">ZebraDesigner Pro v2 barcode label design software makes creating complex labels based on fixed or variable data simple. With ZebraDesigner Pro v2, you enhance your printer\'s capabilities and maximize its performance</string>

    <string name="Zebra_336_IS">The ZXP 3 Load-N-Go cartridges makes it easy to load and replace the ribbon.  They use intelligent media technology for automatic ribbon detection and optimized imaging.  ZXP Series 3 ribbons come in standard and high-capacity, as well as both multi-panel and monochrome options.</string>
    <string name="Zebra_336_IN">The ZXP 3 Load-N-Go cartridges makes it easy to load and replace the ribbon.  They use intelligent media technology for automatic ribbon detection and optimized imaging.  ZXP Series 3 ribbons come in standard and high-capacity, as well as both multi-panel and monochrome options.</string>
    <string name="Zebra_340_IS">The ZXP 3 Load-N-Go cartridges makes it easy to load and replace the ribbon.  They use intelligent media technology for automatic ribbon detection and optimized imaging.  ZXP Series 3 ribbons come in standard and high-capacity, as well as both multi-panel and monochrome options.</string>
    <string name="Zebra_340_IN">The ZXP 3 Load-N-Go cartridges makes it easy to load and replace the ribbon.  They use intelligent media technology for automatic ribbon detection and optimized imaging.  ZXP Series 3 ribbons come in standard and high-capacity, as well as both multi-panel and monochrome options.</string>
    <string name="Zebra_440_IN">I Series 5 panel (YMCKO) Color Ribbon with cleaning roller, 200 Images/roll. The ribbon is used to print in a variety of colors: yellow (Y), magenta (M), cyan (C), and black (K). The remaining overlay (O) provides an extra layer of protection for the card. This ribbon is used to print color on one or both sides of a card. This ribbon is compatible with P330i, P430i, P520i, P310i, P320i, P420i Printers.</string>
    <string name="Zebra_101_Black">ZEBRA 800015–101 Black Ribbon - 1000 images - compatible with Zebra iSeries printers P310i, P320i, P330i, P330m, P420i, P430i and P520i and Zebra C Series printers P300, P310C, P310F, P400, P420C, P500, P520C and P600.</string>
    <string name="Zebra_301_Black">ZEBRA 8  00015–301 Black Ribbon - 1500 images - compatible with Zebra iSeries printers P310i, P320i, P330i, P330m, P420i, P430i and P520i and Zebra C Series printers P310C, P310F, P420C, P500 and P520C.</string>
    <string name="Zebra_PVC_Cards">Zebra\’s Premier PVC Cards are guaranteed to be ISO Compliant for optimal print quality and dust-free cards with smooth edges, time after time. Zebra\’s plastic cards are manufactured to the same high standards that have made Zebra a leader in the ID card industry, for vivid images, and sharp text and bar codes that have no equal.</string>
    <string name="Zebra_Cleaning_Kit">Zebra printer cleaning cartridges, rollers, cards and swabs extend the life of your card printers and improve overall image quality.</string>

    <string name="POS_Jiva_TP_Series">The JIVA 8315E series leads other similar products in terms of its high performance in ultra intensive operation, supported by high end CPU, RAID 1 backup, UPS emergency power, and resistive/IR touch screen. The built in UPS function of JIVA-8315E Series is embedded on main board developed by Posiflex for better stability than others.</string>
    <string name="POS_Monitor">Every POS station requires some kind of POS Monitor and not every business needs a touchscreen. Most retail based POS systems scan or key items in and will use a standard monitor due to the cost savings. We carry a wide range of monitors from 12" to over 47" with options for desktop or wall mount models to fit any application.</string>
    <string name="POS_DT_Series">Resistive touch screen 8” LCD 800 x 600 resolution. Equipped with Intel Pine View D525 Dual Core 1.8GHz CPU with DDR3 memory.UPS Embedded on board developed by Posiflex support to avoid sudden loss of power during transaction. Built-in programmable keyboard. 4 serial ports to support peripheral devices in diverse industrial applications. Various I/O ports support like LAN 10/100/1000 Mb, CR for 2 cash drawers, and 4 USB ports.Easy LCD tilt adjustment from 15degree to 90 degree.Push-open cover to protect power switch from accidental shutdown</string>
    <string name="POS_FT_Series">Look no further! The all new Posiflex FT Series fanless POS terminal has all of above and much more! Looking for performance? Intel Core i5 CPU provides more than enough power for any daily POS related task imaginable. Looking for expandability? Wide array of I/O options, including PCIe expansion slot, are available to meet the different connectivity requirements. Looking for reliability? FT Series is designed to run in the harsh and extreme environments, whether it is freezing cold, scorching hot, dusty or greasy. Posiflex patented fanless technology and renowned technical prowess saw to it that FT Series can function reliably without any hiccup in any environment.</string>
    <string name="POS_HT_Series">The HT series boasts high performance in intensive operation, supported by high end CPU and RAID 1 recovery. The HT series is equipped with Intel Core 2 Duo 2.53 GHz, 12inch LCD, and also support versatile peripheral options such as MSR, customer pole display, programmable keypad, card reader, and a wide range of connectivity to meet numerous applications.</string>

    <string name="PX_450">The Primera PX450 Color Printer is a compact, full-color printer designed for use at retail point-of-sale and point-of-issue built-in guillotine cutter. It is ideal for printing coupons, receipts, tickets, name badges, wristbands and other types of narrow-format output. PX450 Color Label Printers include one color ink cartridge, NiceLabel SE Primera Edition design software, printer drivers for Windows XP/Vista and Mac OS x 10.2 or higher, starter roll of receipt/coupon paper, USB 2.0 cable and instructions.</string>
    <string name="RX_900">Print, encode, verify and dispense RFID enabled labels one at a time. Full color, high resolution inkjet printing at speeds of up to 4.5 inch (114mm) per second. Individual ink cartridges for CMYK. The built in UHF reader/encoder module</string>
    <string name="RX_900F">The offered primer color RFID printer is appreciated for its compact design, sturdy construction and high color printing efficiency. For managing the diverse needs of the customers, we offer this primer color RFID printer is various specifications. </string>
    <string name="LP_130">The Primera LP130 laser marking system. Primera Technology partnered with Coherent to develop the Primera LP130 laser marking system, a cost effective, desktop laser marking solution.</string>
    <string name="LX_400">The LX400 Color Label Printer is an inkjet based printer designed to print short run, full color labels at up to 4800 dpi print resolution. The LX400 prints full color photos, text, graphics and bar code labels. Printed labels are virtually scratchproof and waterproof</string>
    <string name="LX_900">LX900 utilizes the latest in high resolution inkjet technology to print brilliant, colorful labels for your products, boxes and packaging. Individual ink cartridges for each color let you replace only the colors that need replacing. You will save time and money on every job you print. Print labels when and where you need them in just the quantities you can actually use.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_no_internet">NoInternet</string>
    <string name="title_activity_softwares">Softwares</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>

</resources>
